Jiaojiao,
are we friends?
Best friends.
Then I'll be straight.
Before your relationship is exposed,
I want to compose for Cheng Qi in the final.
In the second round,
you played for him, right?
He chose the music.
I just played it.
But in the final,
all contestants can choose their own musician
and compose a piece specially.
Xin,
you're the top musician in Yunjing.
He should be the one begging you.
Ms. Zhang will use her guild
to hold a special concert for the top.
Cheng Qi is the favorite to win.
By then,
many musicians will be vying
to compose for him.
So what's the point of my agreement?
Just go straight to him.
If you agree,
he can't say no.
That's true.
Since this is so important to you,
he has to agree,
whether he wants to
or not.
Jiaojiao.
Xin often plays the zither,
which harms her hands.
My invention,
the lingering sound plectrum,
will surely let her know
my feelings.
[I can't let Mengxin and Jiaojiao]
[be hurt by that lecher.]
Thank you.
Move aside, move aside.
Make way, make way.
Thank you.
Thank goodness you're here.
Otherwise, I wouldn't know
when I could get in this door.
In that case,
you should treat me to dinner today.
Consider it my reward.
My dear,
I don't have money.
The money you gave me is not enough.
It's on you.
It's on me.
You have to
agree to her request.
Okay, I agree.
Don't you want to know what she wants?
You know my wife
better than anyone.
She will never hurt me,
right?
There are no outsiders here.
You don't have to call her that.
Then call her
Jiao.
Whatever.
You can talk business now.
I'll go escort the goods.
Take care.
Mr. Cheng,
please.
I've told you my idea.
If you agree,
I'll wait for you here
every day in the future.
We can practice together.
You...
I...
It seems that Su
likes you, Miss Tang.
Don't mention it.
They are both wooden.
A piece of rotten wood.
A tree of iron.
You mean
they like each other.
Or
I can help you.
We three grew up together.
I know him better than anyone else.
Let's talk about composing.
Jia said
you are
the best musician in the capital.
I also want to ask you to compose for me.
I wish us a happy cooperation
and make a splash in the city.
About the book delivery,
did the Su family take on the escort?
They did.
My Lady,
are you really giving him all the book
escort contracts from the Yun Bookstore?
Fu Xiang begged you several times and you refused.
Is it because of Cheng Qi?
Even you can tell.
Cheng Qi wouldn't figure it out.
I have to give him some benefits
to let him know
how to work for me.
Even if he doesn't want to,
Su Yuejiao
can make him do it.
But if he doesn't know his place,
then take him and the escort agency.
This is the agency's first big order.
Everyone should be on their toes,
Especially you,
Bai.
You should reflect on yourself for several days.
Don't think about anything else,
just focus on escorting.
Next,
the Escort Agency may need some more people.
You can let those brothers
you mentioned before come to the Agency.
It seems that he wants to take over.
You don't even have escort.
How can he be the head?
What are you two whispering about?
Faca.
Where is my brother?
Idle people have more gossip.
Busy work can cure all worries.
Busy
is the best medicine for everything.
Teach them how to move goods.
It's laborious.
My new invention,
the easy-moving machine,
will surely shock the capital
and be famous in the country.
Then Mengxin will know
who is the real capable man.
It's better
not to invent it.
I'm exhausted.
Be careful.
Don't break the book.
These guards are useless.
They even need this thing to transport books.
Are you weak or disabled?
You're all useless.
I think we should take over
this business.
Don't ruin the reputation of the Yunshang Book Bureau.
May you make a fortune.
What was that noise just now?
Did you hear it?
Sounds like a dog barking.
What did you say?
What are you doing?
How dare you hit me?
Beat them!
Who wants to lose a leg?
Mr. Fu, you're so powerful.
You're
making a scene here.
Get out.
Miss Zhang,
You can just tell me if you need a delivery.
Why do you hire such a small escort agency?
Miss Zhang
Our escort agency will deliver your goods to the destination.
The goods are packed.
We'll set off right away.
Be careful.
Don't lose the goods.
Yes.
Let's go.
Well...
Who do I do business with
is my own business.
If you keep making trouble,
you can forget
about doing business here.
I understand.
My lord, are you alright?
Where did you go?
Didn't you tell us to get lost?
Then why are you still here?
Hold him.
Slowly.
Well done today.
Thank you all.
You can't go out alone anymore.
What are you talking about?
Call me boss.
Jiaojiao.
Am I your brother?
Brother.
What's wrong with you?
You look pale.
Are you obsessed with wood engraving?
I...
I can't help it.
If you knew,
you wouldn't be calm either.
What happened to Grandpa?
Grandpa!
Alright.
Grandpa is fine.
He might be playing mahjong.
Then why are you in such a hurry?
Cheng Qi.
What about Cheng Qi?
He goes to the tavern every day.
I know that.
Do you know what he's doing there?
What is he doing there?
I've told you my thoughts.
He has a relationship with Tang Xin.
Now that you mention it,
one recites poetry,
the other plays the zither.
Why didn't I think of that?
They really
are a good match.
He
lied to you
and lied to Xin.
I won't let him off the hook.
If you want to treat me as your brother,
you should
let me do this.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to
kill him.
Brother, brother, brother.
Brother.
Do you hate Cheng Qi?
It's none of your business.
Let's work together
to drive Cheng Qi out of the Escort Agency.
How about it?
What do you want to do?
As long as you make Cheng Qi admit
that he likes someone else
and wants to divorce Jiaojiao,
I and his brother
will drive him out of the Agency.
Why me?
You're new here.
You're skilled.
He's easy to believe you.
What's in it for me?
It's my idea.
You want something from me?
Thirty taels.
What?
What do you mean?
The agency never charges for recruitment.
I have no money now.
Only ten taels.
I'll give you another twenty taels after the job is done.
Is that okay?
When the agency is mine,
I won't give you money.
I'll just kick you out.
Brother
We are escorts.
We can't fight all the time.
When you calm down tomorrow,
I'll let you out.
You're back.
Are you tired?
No.
The more escort orders,
the better I feel.
By the way,
I've been too busy these days
to ask you.
How did you get along with Tang Xin?
Very well.
We had a good time.
Her pipa playing
is the best I've heard
in my years in the music house.
With her on board,
the final trial
will be a breeze.
You've already picked a piece?
Not yet.
But once I finish the lyrics,
the melody will naturally follow.
Good.
Once our agreement ends,
I won't stand in your way.
Since Tang Xin has agreed to compose for you,
you should treat her well.
Give her some jewelry,
or cosmetics.
They'll be useful at the Starry Sky Assembly.
Wait.
First, I don't understand.
Second,
it's not necessary.
Of course it is.
You'll thank me
when you understand.
Yicheng,
what does she mean?
What do you mean?
She asked me to buy rouge for Tang Xin,
and said the alliance would not
when the agreement expires.
Who? Who's with me?
My Lord.
It's not me.
You go to Huayue Tower first.
I'll pick you up later.
A younger brother cannot be kept at home.
Why hasn't Cheng Qi come yet?
It's been so long.
He should have bought it by now.
Stop eating seeds.
You always eat seeds here.
But you're so mysterious today.
What do you want to do?
Xin,
you know that
I married Cheng Qi for the Escort Agency.
After I take over,
I will divorce him.
Here is the divorce paper.
Here you are.
Why do you give it to me?
I know
you and Cheng Qi are the same kind of person.
You write lyrics and he writes music.
Aren't you
Bo Ya and his wife?
It's Yu Boya and Zhong Ziqi.
Right, right.
They are a couple.
So don't worry.
If you two are in love,
I won't stop you.
But for now,
you have to keep it a secret for me.
Tell me.
Did your brother say something to you?
If he hadn't reminded me,
I wouldn't have realized
how well
you two match.
I knew it.
It must be Su Yeqi,
that inarticulate block of wood,
who led you, another block of wood, astray.
He saw me drinking with Cheng Qi last time,
and ran away after leaving this.
Jiaojiao,
I do have someone I like,
but it's not Cheng Qi.
It's your brother.
Does my brother know it?
You are really brother and sister.
If he knows,
he won't misunderstand me and Cheng Qi.
You just want to match us up.
It's because
you can't see Cheng Qi's concern about you.
Take it away.
Sir.
Let's talk.
I'm just a scholar.
I don't have much money.
Why do you want to tie me up?
Do you know Su Yujiao from Su's Escort Agency?
She's my wife.
You can't beat her.
Let me go now.
Otherwise,
she won't let you go.
It's you.
Brother Bai.
Why did you tie me up?
Is there any misunderstanding between us?
You shouldn't be in the Escort Agency.
I'm the son-in-law of the Agency.
I shouldn't be in the Agency?
Where should I be?
If you admit you like someone else,
and leave Su Yuejiao,
I'll let you go.
It seems that it's really Su Li's order.
I only love my wife.
It's impossible to separate us.
Beat him until he tells the truth.
Don't run.
Stop.
Why can he run so fast?
Stop running.
Where is he?
Stop.
You're really fast!
Stop!
Stop chasing!
You're really fast!
You're so fast!
Tell me,
will you divorce or not?
No!
Still talking back?
Stop!
Bai Yanli,
what grudges do you have with him?
You tried to hurt him several times.
He doesn't like you at all,
and he's your sister's...
It's not what you think.
Why don't I kill this unfaithful man for you?
You don't listen to me, right?
Then beat me first.
Cheng Yicheng,
help him out.
Okay.
I won't hurt you.
When we get back to the agency,
you better explain everything to me.
My lady, what are you doing here?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Compared to my father's fists,
this was nothing.
I'm sorry you had to suffer.
I made you some medicine.
Drink it while it's hot.
You should teach that Bai Yanli a lesson.
He's so annoying.
I'm still scared when I think about it.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have been able to come back.
If you hadn't dropped this
at the entrance of Huayue Tower,
I wouldn't have known you were in trouble.
Drink it.
My lady,
my relationship with Tang Xin
is just a partnership.
There's nothing improper between us.
I know.
Because Tang Xin
likes your brother.
How do you know?
And I also know your brother likes Tang Xin.
In his eyes,
I took away his two favorite women.
At the beginning of the kidnapping,
I thought it was your brother.
Who knows it's Bai Yanliang.
My brother doesn't want to kidnap you.
He wants your life.
Men are more jealous than women.
No.
For my safety,
I have to help them.
A wooden man
and a proud woman.
I need to stir things up.
But Bai Yanli...
I'll deal with him later.
The medicine is getting cold.
Drink it up.
It's too bitter.
I don't want it.
I'm fine. I don't need it.
Look.
You can't see how much Cheng Qi cares about you.
Is it broken?
It's fine.
It's all because of Bai Yanliang.
He tried to hurt me several times.
You have to take responsibility for this.
What does it have to do with me?
How does it not concern you?
Bai Yanliang
He's seen me as a thorn in his side since he arrived.
But now I finally understand.
He has been forcing me to divorce you,
and even forcing me to say I like someone else.
It must be your uncle who sent him.
Gong Xi and Fa Chai
have also complained to me.
I didn't expect
Su Li still hasn't given up on you.
And...
And what?
He likes you.
He likes me?
He's just straightforward
and stubborn.
I barely spoke to him.
How could he like me?
There are plenty of straightforward people.
Have you ever seen someone like him before?
Su Yuejiao,
from now on,
my life is yours.
I'll do it.
You can't go out alone anymore.
It's rare.
Not only hardworking,
but also loyal,
and down-to-earth.
What a perfect escort.
Where are you going?
Back to Ning'an.
Or I'll be killed.
You quit the contest?
I quit.
I can't even make it to the final
and become disabled.
And this agency has no backing.
Alright, stop acting.
When he comes back, I'll tell him.
Really?
Will you stay if he stops beating you?
After all, the escort business is competitive,
with fluctuating business.
Talent is hard to come by.
No.
Su's Escort Agency has me or him.
Not both.
Fine.
Then you drink the medicine,
and I'll agree with you.
Then I'll drink half of it.
Fine.
Give it to me.
Brother
You didn't just come out now, did you?
For him,
you're actually going to tie up your own brother.
I didn't even tie the rope tightly.
With your strength,
if you use a bit more strength,
I will...
This is medicine.
Oh my god.
Fortunately, Cheng Qi didn't drink it all just now.
Brother.
You go to Huayue Tower to see Tang Xin every day.
You deserve to die.
It's all a misunderstanding, brother.
I'm going to Yue Lao Pavilion.
You have Jiaojiao,
but you still go to ask for a marriage.
You deserve to die more.
Brother,
Jiaojiao said the escort business is up and down.
I'm looking for Meng Feifei to talk about business.
It's all for my wife.
It's all a misunderstanding, bro.
Jiaojiao, what's that medicine?
He's about to faint.
It freaked me out.
I need to help him
catch up with Tang Xin ASAP.
Tell me,
did Su Li make you drive away Cheng Qi?
Yes.
You admit it.
That's why you came to the Escort Agency?
No.
I said my life is yours.
You can take it back at any time.
This is my mother's.
How did it end up in your hands?
My life
was saved by your mother.
Stop!
The child
Over there.
Catch him.
Quick.
My child.
She's been hunted because of me.
I owe you
my life.
If you want to repay me,
come with me.
My mother saved you
expecting nothing in return.
Otherwise, she would have left a trace.
According to the rules of the escort agency,
you've paid your respects to her,
and that's enough.
You can leave now.
Why do you want me to leave?
You're skilled,
and diligent.
You have the potential to be a good escort.
But in our family, escorts protect, not harm.
especially the weak.
My mother believed that.
So do I.
I don't blame you
for helping Su Li.
But you
shouldn't hurt Cheng Qi.
He will hurt you.
I'll protect you.
My mother told me before she died
in the Su's Escort Agency,
the escort is the top priority.
Besides, we haven't taken any escort for years.
I'll take care of myself.
You should have your own things to do.
Take care.